Before
I go to bed, I just
want to say this to y'all.
I I'm not trying to gain favor from the
black community. Y'all respond to some
of my posts thinking that I am concerned
about like black people in America, you
know, distrusting me or not rocking with
me or me pissing y'all off. I don't
care.
I don't care.
I am only interested in gaining favor
with folks who have value systems that
align with community, that align with
the dismantling of a capitalist system
and with the imagining and implementing
of how to do that.
I don't care what race, nation, or creed
you are.
That's all I care about.
So, I just feel the need to illuminate
that because um as proud as I am of my
blackness, of which I am deeply aligned
and committed to and will always
advocate for, I couldn't give two damns
about black people who don't rock with
me because I have been forgotten by the
black community more times than I can
count. I have been on by the black
community more times than I can count.
Okay,
y'all are not my source of salvation or
protection.
But I have a community that is much
bigger that is and that includes black
folks. Look at that.